(The Start of a New Topic)
- Nice to see you. - It's nice to see you.
You know what? I checked your social media.
You posted so many pictures over the weekend.
My social media feed was a mess because of him.
So I thought my posts got pushed down or something.
(A fun run)
(It's the fun version of running.)
(- What a novel way to run. - Hyun Moo will kill the trend.)
(- Running won't be trendy now. - Funny how Kian84 wasn't there.)
(Moomoo opened up new horizons in the world of running.)
All right. On that note, I have a present for Kian84.
Let me give it to him.
- What present? - That was random.
Open it up first. Okay.
- What's this? - What is it?
- What is it? - Why are you crying?
He wrote it by hand.
- What is it? - "Sign-up sheet..."
"for Moomoo's Run Fun."
"You'll be informed of the result in two days..."
"after a separate membership screening."
"You must match your pace to Moomoo's no matter what."
- Will you sign up? - What?
I have to sign up for this?
- Well, why don't you join me? - Us?
- I already made 100 copies. - You have more?
(I see. You made a lot of copies for the sign-up sheet.)
By the way, I'm worried that Moomoo's Fun Run won't get...
a lot of airtime because of the guest...
who's joining us today.
(He's unbelievable.)
The responses from the viewers were crazy.
Actually, this guy healed my soul.
I've been following him since around 2015 or 2016.
- Is that so? - Watching him play...
- was the only joy I had back then. - Really?
- He's a true fan. - He's a true fan.
Kian84, I heard you prepared to speak in English today.
I'm going to try. So you should all try as well.
- Okay. Don't worry about that. - Speak in English.
No problem.
- You stayed in the UK for a bit. - Yes.
(He visited the UK for his exhibition.)
- Right. - I'm the closest among us.
You're the closest?
After the preview of the Rainbow Live,
so many people asked if he was really going to be on our show.
There were so many people who couldn't believe it.
Right. Some asked if it was an AI-generated video.
- Right. - I couldn't believe it either.
He's an attacking midfielder...
known for his quick feet and flexibility.
It's Jesse Lingard from England!
- I can't stay in my seat. - He's coming.
- Jesse! - My gosh.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
(He used to play...)
(for a prestigious club, Manchester United.)
(And this man ruled the English Premier League.)
(A soccer player, Jesse Lingard)
(Throughout his career, his team won the championships 4 times.)
(He also played on the national team for England.)
(His arrival garnered a lot of attention.)
(He's transferring to Korea, not visiting? This is crazy.)
(I can't believe he chose to come to Korea.)
(He surprised the fans by joining the K League in 2024.)
("Manchester United's Player, Lingard, Signs with FC Seoul")
(He's the spearhead, driving FC Seoul's offense.)
(A maestro who can control the games)
(The Pied Piper on the soccer field)
(Captain of FC Seoul, Jesse Lingard)
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Nice to meet you, Jesse. - Hello.
- Na Rae. Hello. - Very handsome.
- He knows her name. - Okay.
This is crazy.
(Gosh, this is crazy.)
Welcome to one of the best TV shows in Korea.
- The biggest TV show in Korea. - Yes.
Can you say hi to our viewers?
- Hello. I'm Jesse Lingard. - Yes.
His Korean is great.
Jesse. Once a brother, forever a brother.
- Okay? - Yes.
- He understood that. - Yes.
- Okay. - Yes.
- He's British too. - Yes.
I'm Brish...
- Brish? - You're a bridge?
- You're a bridge? - Brish.
- A bridge? - I'm...
Tell him...
- your second home is London. - Yes.
- You know the Saatchi Gallery? - London.
- What? - The Saatchi Gallery?
(Advanced English is a luxury for the Brish Man.)
- Gallery. - Saatchi Gallery. Yes.
I... How do you say exhibition in English? An exhibition...
- Exhibition. - I see.
- Really? - Yes. At the Saatchi Gallery.
- In London? - Yes.
Really? Next time you come, you come with me.
- Really? - Oh, my gosh.
- Can we go to London? - Once a brother, always a brother.
- Yes. Come to London. - Together. Okay.
- Come. - Enjoy.
London is cold, though.
- It's cold? - It's cold.
Okay. I'm a hot girl.
- Hot girl. - She's a hot girl. Okay.
(Neighbor Jesse)
- "Neighbor Jesse." - "Neighbor Jesse."
(Current time, 9:30am)
(Lingard is still in dreamland.)
This feels surreal.
(Squirming)
- He's just like us. - Of course.
- Everyone has blackout curtains. - My gosh.
It looks different to me.
(Getting up as soon as he wakes up)
See? It's different.
What is that on your head?
It's called a bonnet.
- What? - It keeps your hair...
nice and neat while you're sleeping.
(Barely awake)
(Sliding open)
I always open curtains in the morning...
to get natural light. You know?
Very cute.
(Thank you.)
- It's cold. - "Cold."
- It is cold these days. - Yes.
It got cold all of a sudden.
(Catching up on last night's news under the blanket)
- He's just like us. - He is just like us.
Sometimes, I go on TikTok for a little bit.
TikTok.
(His mouth agape.)
Hello. I'm a soccer player, Jesse Lingard.
I've been living in Korea for two years now alone.
Why? Why not go to a big club with money?
(The Brish Man can't articulate his question.)
What?
There are so many big clubs, right?
Why did you choose to come to Korea?
I had a lot of offers in Europe and all over the world.
But they were more like 1-year deals or 6-month deals.
- Right. - So...
FC Seoul came to watch me in Manchester train.
They gave me a 2-year contract with a 1-year option.
- Twelve hours... - That's why you decided...
Yes. They flew 12 hours to see me train.
It was an amazing feeling for me,
- to be honest. - That's great.
Did he explain why?
- Why he came to Korea? - So what happened?
The staff of the club went to Manchester United.
That made him want to join FC Seoul.
They made an effort.
Thank you. Welcome to Korea.
Thank you.
- Why are you smiling like that? - What?
- The smile of Korea. - Smile.
(He gets up after checking his social media.)
We have the same drying rack.
(He scratches his head and heads somewhere.)
(Checking himself out as soon as he gets up)
Did it work? The hair cap?
Yes. It works. A bit.
(Satisfied)
(Grabbing)
(He wipes his face.)
A wet wipe?
I like doing that at barbecue restaurants.
- Wiping your face with wet towels? - Yes.
But why did you use a wet wipe?
(Rubbing)
I think I got it from a K-beauty store.
Like facial wipes.
A K-beauty store? Do you like K-beauty store?
Yes.
- I love it too. - Yes.
Their skincare products are the best. You know?
The best skincare products. Okay. I know that.
PDRN.
PDRN?
- What's that? - The salmon shot.
- It's the component from salmon. - Salmon shot?
Retinol.
- Retinol? - Retinol.
- Retinol. Oh, my gosh. - Retinol.
What's retinol good for?
- Retinol. - It's good for skin elasticity.
- Skin elasticity. - Skin lifting. Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
You're an early adopter for beauty products.
- Early adopter for beauty products? - Early adopter?
Good.
We're bonding over a health and beauty store.
(He uses the facial cleansing wipe to wash his face in the morning.)
(He brushes his teeth right away after wiping his face.)
I have many products. You know?
(Filled with cosmetic products)
- He has so many. - That's a lot.
K-beauty.
- It's the best. - Good.
- For gua sha? - For gua sha?
(You do gua sha too?)
- Do you know what that means? - Yes.
Gua sha. Yes, it's for the jawline.
Gua sha relaxes and lifts your muscles.
Yes.
- Seriously. - He understood everything.
- You can carry on a conversation. - Yes. I told you.
(He brushes his teeth while humming.)
(Splashing water to his hair that was covered all night)
(Feeling refreshed)
Hair brush.
He takes good care of his appearance.
(Jesse Lingard, the man who styles himself)
(He finishes up his routine by moisturizing his skin.)
(His morning routine is finished.)
No shower?
I did shower.
(After making his bed,)
(the well-groomed man goes to the living room.)
What a neat house.
- What a view. - The view of the Han River.
- Nice view. - I like an apartment...
with a nice view.
It's always nice to wake up to a nice view.
The interior is in gray and white hues.
- It looks like a hotel room. - Right.
(Jesse Lingard's course of life is seen all over the house.)
They must be from his fans.
(Player of the Month from the club, Player of the Month from the league)
(In a corner of his dressing room,)
(there's an extensive collection of jerseys.)
(Zinedine Zidane)
- Scholes. - My gosh.
(A jersey from Ji Sung, another player from Man United)
I bet everyone wants that.
- I met Ji Sung Park. - Yes.
- He signed a shirt for me. - Okay.
But the rest of the shirts from Brazil, France,
- Zidane's. - Real Madrid, and Barcelona...
were all retro shirts...
I bought in vintage stores.
- In Korea? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
Yes.
I always go to vintage shops...
in Korea. I go to vintage places.
- They weren't from the players? - They weren't from the players.
- We can buy them too. - He's just like us.
- We're the same. - They're in different generations.
- Right. He can't get it from them. - It was a different generation.
(Lingard is also a soccer fan in front of his idols.)
(The soccer fan's house is filled with soccer-related items.)
Wait. That's from "Squid Game."
(A corner of the kitchen has many items from Korea.)
(An autograph of Director Hwang Dong Hyuk)
(The director of "Squid Game")
(He's immersed in the Korean culture as well as Korean beauty products.)
(The mascot of Seoul)
- Hope is your daughter's name. - Yes, it's my daughter's name.
These are my favorite snacks.
The one with the syrup is good.
That's a good one.
- "The Power of Nunchi." - "The Power of..."
What is that?
I think a fan gave it to me as a gift.
- A fan. - Yes.
So he could assimilate well here.
(He starts his morning with a panoramic view of the Han River.)
My gosh. That's a beautiful view.
Wilson.
Are you sleeping well? Yes?
(Sweet)
Let's chill today. Yes?
Rest, Wilson. You work too hard.
Very sweet. You're a sweet guy.
A sweet guy.
(After checking up on Wilson, he walks over to the whiteboard.)
Energy.
They're quotes I live by.
(Be a winner. Everything happens for a reason.)
(Enjoy life. Concentrate.)
(Be positive. No regrets. Be graceful. Stay humble.)
(Leader, love energy, smile)
So I read them every day.
I think it starts the day off in a positive way...
obviously with a good mindset.
I'm grateful to be here another day...
and obviously to be doing what I'm doing...
A professional soccer player was...
always what I wanted to do since a young boy.
I've got to say we've got to be grateful for the opportunity.
I think you're a really positive man.
- Positive. - I always try to be positive.
Every time I do, you know... If there's a bad situation,
I always try to look for a positive outcome.
- He said you healed his soul. - Really?
I really appreciate that. Thank you.
- This is a good day for you. - You know...
- You got your dream as a fan. - Right.
It finally feels like I'm meeting a celebrity now.
- "Finally?" - Hey, we're celebrities too.
(My family doesn't count as celebrities.)
(After reading the quotes he lives by,)
(he writes something down.)
I have...
- a list of all the K League teams. - Okay.
I have goals, assists, chances created...
So it's a record chart?
(He keeps his personal record for every match.)
So I had to write it for the Gangwon game.
(He reviews the game between Seoul and Gangwon.)
He's reviewing it by writing it down.
(2 goals)
That's good.
(He was chosen as the MVP after scoring 2 goals.)
- Nice goal. - My gosh.
Nice header.
(Recharging on positivity as he remembers the glorious moment)
(Humming)
(Lingard brimming with positive energy)
Why is there a fly?
(He's scared of flies.)
I'm on the top floor. How do they get to the top floor?
Korean flies take the elevator.
- The elevator? - Yes.
- For real? - Yes.
- The elevator. - Really?
They can get on the elevator.
- Yes. - Yes.
They really take the elevator to come up.
(Calling)
(Lingard is calling someone.)
Hi.
Hi, sugar.
- "Hi, sugar." - Sugar plum.
- My daughter. - Who is it?
So cute.
- Your daughter. - Yes.
- Daughter. - So cute.
(That's right.)
You're not married?
- No. I'm single. - Not married?
- He's single. - Who?
Yes. She's my daughter.
He's not married, but he has a daughter.
Return?
(Did you get a divorce?)
Two people can give birth to a child,
but don't have to get married as long as they're on the same page.
In Europe, it's like this sometimes.
This is a common thing in Europe.
(I see!)
So I like to speak to my family and daughter quite regularly.
It was just... To be honest, it was...
the time difference.
It's like an 8 or 9-hour difference.
After a few months, you get used to it.
- Very cute. - Gosh, she's so cute.
What an angel.
- Batman. - Batman.
So cute.
What?
This one is called... She's called Wilson.
Hi.
She's adorable.
"Cast Away?" Wilson?
- Three hundred... - Twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand.
Twenty thousand steps?
She went to New York for Halloween.
She walked a lot.
And what are you doing tomorrow?
What are we doing tomorrow?
(Chuckling)
- He adores his daughter. - He looks so happy.
I'm in New York a lot.
(Joking)
That's Korea.
(My daughter is so cute.)
She's a smart one.
- She always makes you smile. - Always.
So now, you're actually in Times Square,
right in the middle.
Why are you laughing?
(He talks to his daughter on the phone, losing track of time.)
Gosh, he looks so happy.
What a sweet daddy you are.
Even if I lose a game or I'm down,
when I call my daughter, I'm always back on.
I'm happy ultimately.
(His affectionate phone call ends.)
(Pulling)
It's cold. So I gave him...
- the hoodie. - It's cold.
- Because it's cold? - It's cold.
(Playful)
How sweet.
He seems to like Wilson a lot.
(After taking care of Wilson, he walks...)
(into the dressing room.)
He's so organized.
(His clothes are neatly organized.)
You love clothes.
(There are also various types of hats.)
Well, yes. I always like to try to look good. You never know...
who you're going to meet. So it's always important...
to keep the standard high in the fashion world.
(Unique fashion styles)
Yes. It's always nice to get recognition.
(Like a fashionista, he owns rows and rows of shoes.)
- He is indeed a fashionista. - Of course.
(Thinking)
(He carefully picks out his outfit.)
(He spends quite some time to pick out an outfit.)
Let's go.
(After picking out the outfit, he turns on the Bluetooth speaker.)
(Beeping)
I always play music in the morning.
Now, the shower.
(I can see that.)
- Gosh. - My goodness.
- Oh, my gosh. - That's a great body for soccer.
Oh, my gosh. I knew it.
- Athletes have the best body. - He's the real deal.
- Yes, he is. - MINHO was fake.
- He's the real deal. - Right.
(He comes back to the dressing room.)
(He pulls out the ironing board.)
- It's hard to use that properly. - That's interesting.
A little bit.
Iron it a little bit.
Ta-da.
Just a little bit.
(Gently ironing a bumpy part)
He's good at this.
Gosh, how professional.
- Ironing a hoodie is really hard. - Right.
He can only do this because he loves clothes.
(Will it look better now?)
(He puts on the hoodie after ironing it.)
(It's perfectly pressed.)
(He spritzes on some cologne.)
(He's ready to go out.)
Wilson, you're security. Yes?
Take care of my house, please.
He sounds so cool when he talks to Wilson.
(Let me pick out my shoes too.)
(Putting it on)
The shoelaces look nice.
I'm hungry.
It feels surreal to watch this.
It's weird. The more I watch it,
the more it gives the AI-generated video vibe.
(Humming a melody)
Yes, Seongsu.
Yes. I mean, it's only 3 or 4 minutes away.
There are always a lot of pop-up shops.
- There are so many. - That's a fun neighborhood.
The main street is always busy as well.
- Ju Seung and I ran there. - Right.
I'd like to have a little walk down there.
It's good to get out...
and like I said, to be around a lot of people.
Jesse.
Hello.
- Of course, they all recognize him. - Jesse!
(People are calling his name from all directions.)
How do you feel when people call you Jesse?
It's good because normally,
- in England, they say Lingard. - Lingard.
They say, "Lingard."
In Korea, they say, "Lingard" with an accent.
- You know? - "Lingard."
When they say Jesse, it's more normal and natural.
They see Lingard as a soccer player.
But I'm really like Jesse, the human person. The normal person.
- He prefers to be called Jesse. - Jesse is good.
They call him like their friend.
(Jesse quickens his steps.)
(Rushing)
(He grabs people's attention wherever he goes.)
Everyone must be so star-struck.
- Right. - Even we're star-struck.
(Opening the door powerfully)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Where is this place?
(Jesse goes up the stairs right away.)
It's a clothing store.
Did he go shopping?
(He strides past the clothes.)
- Hello. - Hello.
This way, please.
- What? - They have a restaurant...
- on the 3rd and 4th floors. - I see.
Hello. GG.
- GG? - GG.
You're late.
- This is great. - What?
- I see. - It's Kim Jin Su.
It's Kim Jin Su.
- He's a left back. - I see.
He has a similar role to Lee Young Pyo.
He plays defense for the national team.
I'm hungry, bro.
- I'm hungry. - Seriously, bro.
Do you guys meet in private often too?
It's important for team bonding as well. You know?
- Did you check the menu? - What?
- Did you check the menu? - Yes.
A special gourmet cheeseburger.
What?
- Yes. That's good. This one. - You know?
- This one. - And you?
The cheeseburger is top-tier, bro.
Okay. I'll take...
- scrambled eggs and hash browns. - Okay.
- Excuse me. - "Excuse me."
He can call a waiter.
- One of this. - Okay.
And...
- Matcha with vanilla syrup. - Okay.
Yes.
- Matcha. - Matcha.
That's your own recipe, right?
In my matcha, I add one pump of vanilla syrup.
Okay. One pump of vanilla syrup.
- Vanilla syrup. - It's good.
- It's good. - It's good.
Hyun Moo, it's time for you...
- Yes. - to try matcha.
- Then... - I'll try that in two weeks.
No. Don't drink matcha.
- Your kids woke up early? - Yes.
Always.
My kids never stop...
- Yes? - running or shouting.
- He's a dad too. - Thank you.
That's the conversation for dads.
(Asking about his kids first)
How old is she now?
Six years old.
So they're the same age.
- My daughter. - Same age.
When is your family coming to Korea?
- Not this year? - Not this year. No.
I'll go back home for Christmas...
- He must miss his family. - and spend Christmas there.
Are you lonely being alone here?
Lonely?
Is living in Korea lonely?
No, because I have my friends...
I have my friends from soccer. So we can go for dinner. You know?
- Not lonely since you have soccer? - Or lunch.
I spoke about you.
"I'm going to meet Jesse."
And then beside my baby, she went,
"What?"
"You're going to meet Jesse?"
"Why aren't you taking me?"
- "I like him." - We're at a bar.
His daughter must be a huge fan.
And then my daughter asked me,
"What does this mean?"
- You don't know what it means? - No.
(It's Jesse's signature gesture.)
That's Jesse's signature.
J and L.
- I see. - Oh, my gosh.
- Jesse Love. - J and L.
It's Jesse Lingard.
- Jesse Lingard. - I see. They're his initials?
- Lingard. - Jesse Love? Seriously?
- Jesse Love. - Jesse Love.
- We love Jesse. - I mean, it could be.
- Or Jesse Lucky? - Jesse Lucky.
- Jesse Love. - Okay.
He has a lot of gestures.
This one.
- This is another one. - Okay.
- What's that one? - Then there's the dab.
- Dab? - The one with the pipe.
- The pipe? - Yes.
(It goes like this.)
- Do you know this one? - Of course, I know.
I have many ceremonies.
I'm starving, bro. Seriously.
Excuse me. When will our food be served?
- "When will our food be served?" - When will our food be served?
He speaks good Korean.
- We learn essential phrases first. - Right.
When will our food be served?
(Right now)
Thank you.
That looks good.
(Cheeseburger with scrambled eggs and hash browns)
Hash browns.
Enjoy your food.
Jesse. You were born in December 1992, right?
Yes. You?
June 1992.
Speak to me with honorifics.
- You're 32 years old now. - Yes.
- December 31. - I'm older.
- Okay. - Yes.
Say, "Enjoy your food, sir."
Enjoy your food, sir.
You start. I can't eat until you eat.
- You know that? - Gosh.
- Okay. - How does he know that?
- You... - I'll start.
I'll start eating. Okay.
- Okay. - Enjoy your food.
- It's yummy. - Yes.
(He finally has a bite after his older friend has a bite.)
That's getting me home.
(The older friend by 6 months has a bite.)
(The younger friend has a bite.)
- Yes? - Yes.
(They enjoy their meal while keeping their manners.)
(Sipping on his matcha drink)
I bet it tastes great.
Right. I have something to show you.
Lingard.
(His heart is melting.)
Hello, Lingard.
- My gosh. - It's Jin Su's daughter?
(Jin Su's daughter does Jesse's goal celebration.)
She knows every ceremony.
- Right. - Then she's a big fan of yours.
- Yes. - So cute.
Hello, Lingard. I love you very much.
- So cute. I swear. - My daughter.
I asked my daughter.
"Sonny or Jesse?"
Jesse, 1st. Sonny, 2nd.
I asked, "And me?"
"Not you, Daddy."
- Uncles are the best. - "Not you, Daddy."
He's got a wonderful family.
He's very family-oriented...
which is important because I am too.
Sometimes, I think having a life outside soccer is also important.
It's important to have a good relationship off the field.
Then obviously, on the field, it's going to be even better.
He's the captain. So he's thinking about that aspect.
- Energy is good this week. - Yes.
- Yesterday, it was tough training. - Yes.
- Nobody complained. - Nobody complained.
We need your experience. Yes.
Please teach the other players.
It's good that the players listen. You know?
Tomorrow, we'll speak to them a little bit.
- We need to speak before the game. - Yes.
Let this week also be a good one. Please, my captain.
- Let's go. - Okay. Let's go.
Let's go. Okay.
Okay.
The meal was great.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you, Captain. - I love this.
Thank you.
Please get in.
(They will head out together in Jin Su's car.)
Jesse.
Yes. Thank you.
- Okay, bro. How are you? Good? - I followed you for a while.
- Thank you, bro. - Can I take a picture?
Yes. Come.
It's the same guy that followed me from before.
(A fan was surprised to run into Jesse.)
- I see. - And he followed me from before.
Yes. He was waiting for you? To say hi?
To take a picture? Oh, my.
(Taking a picture with a fan who waited for a long time)
- Nice to meet you. Thank you, bro. - You too.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(He's sweet to his fans wherever he is.)
Please make it tasty.
- "Make it tasty?" - "Make it tasty."
I'm so full, bro.
Let's go.
I'm the best of the best drivers.
- Yes? - Yes.
(Let's get going now.)
It's "Golden."
- "Demon Hunters?" - Yes. "Demon Hunters."
"KPop Demon Hunters."
- I see. - I see.
My baby always...
- She plays this song? - Yes.
And dances to this song?
- Kids love it. - It's a huge hit among the kids.
They love "KPop Demon Hunters."
I need to start as soon as possible.
- Maybe, I've heard it. - Yes.
I heard "Golden" a lot.
- Yes. I heard it a lot. - Yes.
(Swaying)
(Dancing)
- It's catchy. You know? - Very catchy.
Dance to the music.
My gosh. You're a good dancer.
- He's known for his dancing. - Okay.
- Really? - Has he always been that way?
- Really? - One of his best friends is...
a soccer player named Pogba.
- Pogba. - We know who he is.
They've been close since they were young.
Reels or shorts of them dancing together...
have often gone viral.
- He can dance very well. - To me,
they're like the celebrities' challenge videos.
Do you still remember Pogba and you dancing together?
- Yes. Always. When we scored, - He knows everything.
we used to dance and celebrate together.
They were a fantastic duo.
- Really? - The best duo.
They were a good pair.
The weather is nice.
- Guri. - Guri.
Guri.
- Let's go, bro. - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
All right.
- Hey, the weather is nice. - The weather is nice.
- The weather is nice. - The weather is nice.
(My goodness)
(Impressed)
This team has many fans.
My heart is pounding.
(It's where the athletes in Seoul train their bodies.)
(The captain of FC Seoul, Lingard)
- The atmosphere is different. - All right.
He has charisma.
(The former premier leaguer in the K League's training field)
- Hello. - Hello.
He's saying hello to the older women.
- It's so nice to see that. - Yes.
The ladies work so hard every day...
to help fix the field.
Every morning and every afternoon, they're out there fixing the field.
- He has gratitude... - Yes.
- for people who clean the field. - He's polite.
Hello.
- Lingard, good luck. - Good luck.
- Good luck. - They're so sweet.
Yes.
Bro.
(He arrives at the field.)
Pass the ball.
Are you okay, bro?
- Of course. - Are you good?
(He brings up his energy as he says hello to his teammates.)
I got caught, you know.
(Let's train. Gather around, everyone.)
Let's go.
(The training begins in earnest.)
(They start with a light stretch.)
(Quick)
FC Seoul fans will love this.
- Sprint. - My goodness.
(Stretching)
Training always needs to be done with good vibes, you know.
A warmup is always done with good vibes.
Laughing and joking.
That's fascinating.
- He improves the mood. - Yes.
(His movements are quick.)
(The players are gathered around after warming up.)
Pass possible.
(The players pass the ball with speed.)
Hey.
(A rondo is a well-known passing drill.)
Good.
There you go.
Last year, sometimes, we didn't do it in the morning.
Before training, we didn't do a rondo.
I said, "Coach, hey, we need to do it every day."
We do that every day, bro.
(A rondo drill became a routine due to Lingard's suggestion.)
It sets that atmosphere for training, you know.
Here we go.
- That way. One, two, three. - One, two, three.
Four, five.
- Three. - Three.
(He sees a charging defender and uses a feint!)
(He has footwork that suits his position of the captain.)
One, two,
three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- No! - Out.
(Unhappy)
Hey, guys. Hey, focus. Keep these two.
Keep these two.
Yes. Focus.
(Jesse leads the players as the captain.)
- Hey. - One, two, three,
four, five.
(The atmosphere turns serious afterward.)
One, two,
three, four...
Seven, eight.
(Giggling)
(He makes the atmosphere less serious again.)
(Laughing)
(The captain trains as he enjoys himself with his teammates.)
They train as if they were playing.
- One. - Hey.
(They have a shooting drill as well.)
- That startled me. - Seriously.
- He's a total extrovert. - He's an energizer.
During training, I'm so loud.
(For about 3 hours and 30 minutes,)
(they train until the sun sets.)
(They return to the locker room with their tired legs.)
(The sky turned dark while he was training hard.)
(Crowded)
- Seongsu is trendy. - There are so many people.
(Jesse comes back to Seongsu-dong after training.)
(He walks in a relaxed way.)
(He enters a bright building.)
- What's this? - Where is he?
(The place is full of people.)
(It has many trendy beauty products.)
A beauty store?
- Is it the K-beauty store? - You have to go there.
- K-beauty store? - K-beauty store.
(The healthy Seongsu man is serious about skincare.)
(He slathers on lotion as soon as he wakes up.)
(The beauty enthusiast, Jesse, even irons his clothes.)
(He gets on the elevator as if he was familiar with the place.)
(Shall I go and protect my skin?)
(What are the K-beauty products...)
(of Jesse, the former premier leaguer?)
(Jesse is at a K-beauty store.)
(Looking around)
(He grabs a shopping bag.)
The way he grabbed the bag tells me that he has visited often.
(Walking around)
(The beauty enthusiast, Jesse, spots something.)
(It's a collection of sheet masks.)
- Hey. - Sheet masks.
(He scans the items carefully.)
(Fascinated)
(Grabbing)
(Okay, I'll get this one.)
(He picks one and puts it inside the bag.)
(He grabs another one.)
It's okay.
(He puts it in the bag again.)
Do you have your own standards of selecting the sheet masks?
I don't pick them based on the brands.
Like I said, I used PDRN.
- PDRN. - PDRN.
- Yes. PDRN. Very good. - I should memorize that too.
Tea tree, hyaluronic acid, collagen...
Yes. One hundred percent. They make my skin smoother.
Everybody wants the glass look, you know. The glass skin.
- Yours is very good. - Thank you.
(A sudden compliment)
Shiny skin. It's very shiny.
- He takes care of his skin. - Thank you.
- He takes care of his skin. - Like me. Like my skin.
- It looks good too. Yes. - Okay.
It took him 7.5 seconds to answer.
- "How should I say it?" - It was the speed...
- of a fun run. - A fun run.
- It was like a fun run. - It was the speed of a fun run.
How old do you think he is based on his skin?
What do you think?
- Maybe... - Look.
(Maybe...)
Thirty-six?
- Thirty-six? - Thirty-six?
Did he think Hyun Moo was born in 1936?
For goodness' sake.
He meant to say 63.
He was reading "The Power of Nunchi" diligently.
He knows how to read the room.
(He has adjusted to Korea perfectly with "The Power of Nunchi.")
- Thank you for your comment. - He's 60.
Sixty? What?
She's joking. No.
He's a grandpa.
(He's closer to 60.)
(Using his cellphone, he looks for a product he wants.)
Hello.
- Eye patches? - Yes, eye masks.
And my skin is sometimes dry, you know.
- So I need... - In that case...
This product contains vitamin C.
- It's good. - It's nice.
Thank you.
I picked one already. This one.
- Is it good? - It's very good.
- Is it good? - Yes, it's very good.
- I know. - Yes, it's very good.
(I know.)
- And facial cream. - Facial cream.
PDRN.
- PDRN. - PDRN. Yes.
Had we had the trending searches, "PDRN" would've taken first place.
- Is it good? - Yes. It's a bestseller.
Is it the best?
Okay. I'll take one.
There are capsules. Once they're melted,
the skin becomes smooth and moist.
- Is it good? - Yes, I'm using this too.
- Two. - Two.
(Since it's good, I'll take two.)
Yes.
Two.
Since it was a good item, you took two.
- Thank you. - It's good. Okay.
Am I really seeing this with my own eyes?
It's like seeing the Avengers at a gimbap place.
It's like seeing Timothee Chalamet eat bindaetteok...
- at a traditional market. - I know.
- That's right. - Foreigners will say...
that it's a photoshopped image.
- It isn't an AI-generated image. - It isn't a deepfake.
(It isn't an AI-generated image.)
(There's a former premier leaguer in a K-beauty store.)
Let's pay.
(The line for payment is long.)
That's where customers pay.
- It's a self-checkout. - A self-checkout.
(There are kiosks for a self-checkout.)
You can do it.
- Try it. - He's relaxed.
Okay.
(There's an empty kiosk!)
(Beeping)
(He scans the barcodes with ease.)
He's good.
(The total is 227.10 dollars.)
(My goodness)
It's okay.
(He's cute.)
(With a full shopping bag,)
(the beauty enthusiast, Jesse, goes somewhere.)
The door is open.
(He returns to his dark home alone.)
The door is locked.
That's the sound of Korea.
The sound of coming home after work.
Wilson.
How was your day, bro? Good?
Was it a good day in the house?
His ears might hurt.
(Laughing)
(He plops down on the sofa.)
(Pressing)
- Streaming time. - Yes.
Chill.
(He sets the audio to Korean.)
- Why? - Does he want to study?
You have to understand the characters, you know.
- That's impressive. - That's right.
(He opens up his ears to Korean and watches diligently.)
What do you watch?
- Yes, you must watch it in Korean. - "K-Pop Demon Hunters."
- You must watch it in Korean. - Yes.
- "Demon Hunters?" - Yes, "Demon Hunters."
I need to start as soon as possible, bro.
(He watches it today.)
(We love you, Huntrix.)
(He focuses on the Korean lines.)
It's a signal from the front floor.
- It's a delivery. - A delivery.
I'm 100 percent sure that it's a delivery.
I'm so hungry.
- I'm so hungry. - You're hungry.
(He ordered a delivery while he was outside.)
His phone is shattered.
You need to change your phone.
I changed it.
Food?
I wonder what he'll eat.
Wilson.
I'm hungry, Wilson.
(Poor Wilson)
Seriously.
(He has a one-sided conversation all day long.)
I'm so hungry.
(He carefully takes out today's dinner.)
Isn't that fried chicken?
Fried chicken?
(Fried chicken and the wing set)
Fried chicken was...
It was the top, you know.
Did you order two for yourself?
Two chickens?
I wanted to try different flavors.
That's right.
He ordered four sauces.
He wants to try each one.
(Which flavor should I try first?)
(He picks up a wing and dips it in mustard.)
(Eating)
My goodness.
- He eats with gusto. - I can taste the flavors.
- It's really tasty. - Yes, it's really tasty.
(It's an evening with K-culture.)
(Crunchy)
It looks tasty.
He's dipping it well.
(It goes straight into his mouth.)
How does he eat it so well?
I couldn't stop. I was so hungry.
(He dived into the food.)
(Tapping)
(Vibrating)
(He calls someone.)
What are you eating now?
Chicken.
For real.
- My friend. - Your friend.
(In the morning, he had a video call with his daughter, Hope.)
(He shares the evening with his friend.)
Really?
(Laughing)
(This is the Korean fried chicken.)
(Doesn't it look tasty? Take this.)
- You're teasing him. - Yes. It's because...
he likes chicken as well, you know.
- Yes. - Yes.
Very nice.
(He inhales chicken for his friend to see.)
I'm sitting here laughing.
- All right. Good. Later. - Later.
(He finishes the call with his friend.)
Little soda pop
- Little, little soda pop - "Little soda pop."
I'll put the chicken in the fridge.
- The remaining food... - Will he eat it tomorrow?
That's right. I put chicken in the fridge.
- Tomorrow? - I'll eat it tomorrow.
Leftover chicken is tasty.
(After storing the leftover chicken)
(Water running)
Music again.
(Dancing)
(The cheerful Lingard is happy after showering on a full stomach.)
(He applies lotion as he sings along.)
(He moisturizes his entire body.)
He's thorough.
Seriously.
(He moisturizes his entire body.)
(Let's check out the beauty products I bought.)
- This is a new one you just bought. - Yes.
It's fun to use the product you just bought.
- That's right. - That's right.
(Ripping)
(He puts the fresh sheet mask on his face.)
He's taking care of his skin.
He's the master of skincare.
No clinics?
- Clinics. - Clinics?
Don't you go to beauty massage shops or skin care clinics?
- Yes, I go there. - You go there?
- In Korea as well? - Tomorrow, I'll go there.
He takes good care of his skin.
To do what?
I do all. I do the hair rejuvenation,
- skin care... - Skin care.
- Yes. - Skin care. Everything.
I never thought that I'd relate to a soccer player,
- Jesse Lingard. - I feel much closer to him.
Good.
My heart began to pound...
- when he mentioned PDRN. - Same here.
PDRN.
- PDRN? - What's PDRN?
- What's PDRN? - Salmon injections.
When you first said PDRN,
I became your biggest fan.
(Picking up)
Gosh, he likes that snack.
He has old people's taste in snacks.
- It's tasty. - It's tasty indeed.
- It's so tasty. - The flavor is traditional Korean.
- It's tasty. - It's tasty.
You know, you need to go home, literally switch off, and just rest.
He calls a lot.
(Jesse calls someone as he opens his late-night snack.)
How are you doing?
It's my mother.
(Lingard's mother)
She's his mother.
His mother was a gymnast.
- Really? - Yes.
Am I doing this right?
You need to lie down a bit.
It split. Look.
Yes.
(He takes off the sheet mask that split.)
Oh, my gosh.
I'll put another one on later.
I went to see my friend.
- She came here for a holiday, so... - Yes.
(In the morning, he had a video call with his daughter, Hope.)
(In the evening, he talked to his friend over dinner.)
(At night, he's sharing his day with his mom.)
- Yes? - Are you sleeping tight?
When is your last match?
What are you watching?
Well...
That's the same for everyone.
It can't be helped when you live alone.
What I heard was that you always lived with your family in London.
- I mean, in England. - Yes.
When I was in Manchester, my family was close anyway...
and my friends were always around.
This is my first time being really like,
away from my family and my daughter for a long time.
So you feel good or what?
It's nice. I can go home and just chill.
Nobody will bother me, you know?
I can just sit on my sofa and enjoy streaming services.
- I can watch movies. - We're all the same.
We're all the same.
To live alone, I feel at peace.
I think I just enjoy every day, you know?
Be positive. It's important to have good people around you.
I've met so many great teammates...
with the same vibe and same energy.
I just enjoy every day being around that energy.
(Everyday, Full of Joy)
(That was great.)
When I watched a lot of the Premier League,
that was when I just started making music...
and I had a strong desire to do well.
At around that time, Jesse also had to show his talent.
He always had a smile on his face and he seemed to enjoy it,
so he gave me a very positive influence.
That's really good.
- I loved how positive he was. - Right.
- His positive nature? - Yes.
I highly recommend that he should try using hyaluronic acid.
We have prepared a small gift for you.
Probably, your daughter might like it...
- very much. - Okay.
(Curious)
It can't be hidden.
Ta-da!
Wilson.
- It's a new one. - It's a new one.
- My best friend! - Yes.
My best friend, Wilson.
- Do you like it? - I have to put his hood up.
Oh, right.
(He hides his ears in the hood like a habit.)
- Thank you. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I have a gift for all of you as well.
- Really? - Yes.
- Really? - A gift for all of us?
- What is that? - Gosh, what a surprise.
- Is it a soccer ball? - Gosh.
- What did you prepare for us? - What is that?
Please.
Oh, my gosh!
- Gosh! - Their uniforms!
- Is your name on it? - I signed them with your names.
- Gosh, Kian84! - Gosh, Kian84!
Your names.
(Signed uniforms with their names)
- Signed uniforms? - Gosh!
- CODE KUNST. - What a successful fan!
- A successful fan, indeed. - A successful fan.
It was even written in Korean.
- KEY, that's me. - KEY.
- Thank you. - KEY.
I wonder who this could be?
- Oh, my gosh! - Maybe it's for Wilson?
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- No! - Gosh!
- Wilson. - Thank you!
(Uniforms signed by Jesse with all five of their names)
- Thank you very much! - Thank you!
- Thank you. - You love it.
Let's invite him to our next Sports Day.
- Let's do that. - Right.
We'll pack our lunches again.
- Thank you. - Thank you. It's been amazing.
Thank you very much, guys.
(Return of Bacterrius)
- "Bacterrius." - "Bacterrius."
"Return of Bacterrius."
- Have a good day. - Have a good day.
Bye.
(Woo Il is in his tracksuit and his hair is messy.)
(His hair is neat today.)
One might think you're the soccer player.
You look great.
- You look really nice today. - It's like "A Better Tomorrow."
- You look really nice. - Right.
Wearing an outfit like this...
- makes my voice go lower. - Right.
- Your hair looks nicer as well. - Right.
He might cut his hair now.
(Glossy)
(Woo Il comes out from somewhere.)
Where is this?
- A hot spring? - A hot spring?
It's a bathhouse.
Winter has already come!
- Nice! - You're still passionate!
(Woo Il still has his passion.)
(He gets into a car.)
You drive a Genesis?
- Right. - Gosh.
But isn't it fine for him to drive a car like that?
There were rumors that you have been drinking wine.
I'm half-90.
- You're half-90? - Yes.
I would've been dead if this was the Joseon Dynasty.
- Half-90. - Right.
It's fine for me to drive that kind of car now.
Nice to meet you. I'm half-100.
- Half-100. - Right.
It was a used car.
My friend sells used cars...
and I got it for a cheap price from him.
We only saw you driving your bike.
We thought you only had a bike.
- You thought I didn't have a car? - Right.
- It doesn't look like your car. - Is that so?
I do have a car.
(He heads out with the used car he bought.)
(He feels refreshed after a bath.)
It seems like it's really early in the morning.
- It looks like the countryside. - Right.
(He arrives somewhere in the countryside.)
(He gets out a big bag.)
Where could this be?
- Isn't that a gym bag? - This is it.
- You all won't know. - Right.
- I have no idea. - Right.
- It's hard to predict this place. - Where is this?
(He gets something out of his bag as soon as he arrives.)
There.
- What is that? - Baseball?
Do you play baseball?
- Baseball? - Do you play baseball?
It's a hobby that needs that kind of outfit.
(Horseback Riding Club)
- Horseback riding? - Horseback riding?
Horseback riding?
(At the place Woo Il came to early in the morning,)
(it's filled with horseback riding equipment.)
The boots look great.
I know it doesn't suit me,
but I've done a bit of horseback riding.
It must suit you with your long hair.
(He has been horseback riding for a while.)
Horseback riding is really impressive.
Actually, that was when...
- I didn't have much work to do. - Right.
I wondered if there was a way for me...
to make a living in that field.
It was to work in that field?
- I can totally relate. - The niche market.
- Right. - That was why I learned DJing.
- Right. It was for the same reason. - DJing. It was because...
- I didn't have any work. - Right.
I had to learn something during that time.
But why didn't you continue working there?
I got myself into that niche market,
but that field didn't need comedians.
I was a sportscaster.
Let's say a horse named Speed goes by.
"There's Speed!" If I shout it out like that,
- then I'm told to be quiet. - Right.
- The horse shouldn't get startled. - Right.
The horse had to go over obstacles and such.
(Horseback riding commentating is rather calm.)
(Im Woo Il)
(That's right.)
It had to be fairly quiet,
- Right. - including the commentating.
(He does horseback riding as a hobby instead of work now.)
(He gets properly dressed.)
(He even puts on his helmet!)
Gosh, that's impressive!
Gosh!
You look like a foreign equestrian.
You have really long legs.
- Right. - The outfit looks nice.
- The outfits look nice. - Right.
You need the right equipment for horseback riding.
I have all of the equipment.
- You need the equipment. - You have your own equipment?
Yes. Back then, I thought it was an investment.
It was an investment...
- to get into that field. - This is what it feels like today.
It feels like you're trying to explain yourself.
It's not a hearing today.
- There's no need to be like that. - First,
- say that you're sorry. - Right.
I apologize for drinking wine.
No! What's wrong with that?
- I apologize for horseback riding. - Genesis.
Right.
I apologize for driving a Genesis.
You don't have to explain yourself. Be confident.
- Of course. - Understood.
(He confidently gets his equipment.)
I bought some carrots for the horses.
- I see. - Gosh, thank you so much.
Right.
- Cookie! Gosh, Cookie. - Yes.
(Have you been doing well, Cookie?)
Are you renting a horse as well?
- From the stable. - A rented horse.
The horses have their own owners.
I'm riding the horses there.
- They all have their owners. - Right.
Hey, Cookie.
Cookie is a horse that I got on several times.
- I see. - Right.
Cookie looks so pretty.
Gosh, you want some don't you?
(I brought carrots, Cookie.)
Do you want some? Here you are.
(Crunch)
(Chewing)
Cookie is enjoying it.
(The horse seems to be grateful for Woo Il's efforts.)
- Gosh! - Cookie is really enjoying it.
The horse looks fascinating. It's like a giraffe.
The horse looks pretty.
Okay.
(It's good.)
After a few months,
the horses felt like dogs.
(Connecting)
You can connect with a horse...
just like a dog.
Have all of it.
(Sweet)
Got it? Have some more after chewing everything.
We have to do well together. Got it?
- We have to do well together. - It's a meek horse.
Got it?
Okay. There we go.
(Let's get some exercise now that we've connected.)
(He heads into the training center full of excitement.)
(He moves to the other side of Cookie.)
All right.
Hey, Cookie.
- Hey, Cookie. - Hold the reins.
(The man who gets on the white horse)
(Bacterrius)
(Terrius)
- "Bacterrius." - Terrius.
- You're not scared anymore, right? - No.
- It must be scary at first. - It does feel scary at first.
It feels like you're much higher up on the horse.
- Gosh. - Right.
- Okay. - The reins are ready.
- Walk. - Right.
All right.
(Let's go!)
Forward.
- Cookie must be a good horse. - Right.
- Walk comfortably. - Right.
(They start with a simple warmup.)
He looks like a prince of a country.
(The warm sunlight shines through the windows.)
(The prince on the white horse moves gracefully.)
(Am I the one to become King?)
It's a great sight.
Walking is the simplest form of moving.
I give signals to the horse with my foot.
I give a single kick during the walk.
The trot is next.
The trot is like a power walk.
It's a faster walk.
Your back has to be like that.
I have to bounce up and down like that.
- I have to move like that. - That's fascinating.
You'll hurt your back if you don't do that.
That also makes the horse...
- feel less exhausted. - Right.
Moving up and down helps the horse move better.
That's impressive.
I'm not just sitting comfortably on the horse.
I have to stay fixed on the horse with my thighs.
Your adductor muscles have to suffer so much.
I constantly have to strain my lower body.
It brings up your hips as well.
I heard horseback riding is great for women.
Right.
Keep going.
(The adductor muscles are fixed as he moves his back.)
(He works on the pace with Cookie.)
- Check the direction. - Gosh.
- His hair is flying in the air. - Good.
Let's warm up outside.
(Groaning)
My back is hurting already.
(They move outside.)
- Do the same thing outside. - Right.
- Let's go. - It feels like England.
You look like a nobleman!
- It feels like Buckingham. - Right.
- Shall we go with the canter now? - Okay.
(Let's go, Cookie!)
There you go.
I give all of the signals with my foot.
(The canter begins with his signal.)
(Cookie picks up the pace.)
(Moving up and down)
(The canter is done with a stable form.)
- I did some running today. - Gosh.
Look at you.
He's good at this.
Your form looks great.
- You're doing well. - Well, he did do it for a year.
Right. Just like that.
(The one who rides through the open field)
(Terrius on a white horse)
(Don't fall asleep, Princess.)
(I am right here.)
Enjoy it even more.
(Hair flying in the air)
You look like a rich man!
(Did he buy a white horse with his own money?)
It's like "The Rose of Versailles."
- He's just like Terrius today. - On his way to meet the princess.
(Terrius)
(Will you not hurry?)
(I'm on my way to meet the princess!)
Rest and turn. Warm up.
Slowly.
- Your form looks good today. - Great job.
Gosh, this is exhausting.
The prince on the white horse lacks so much stamina.
That was just the warmup.
The course we did the other time.
Let's go through that course.
Go around and go to number two toward the end.
You're going over obstacles?
- You're doing that? - That must be really hard to do.
It's hard to memorize the order.
(There are various obstacles with numbers.)
It's really confusing to memorize the course.
I have to go to number 1 and turn to go to number 7.
I have to move back and forth with the same obstacle.
- You have to be smart to do this. - Right.
So before I start,
I go around the course to show the horse.
"You go here and there."
- Just like for dogs. - Dog agility?
- Right. The dogs go here and there. - Just like that?
- Dog agility. - Just like that,
- I show the horse what to do. - When you get it wrong,
you know how you must do it until you get it correct, right?
Right.
It's just the same. The horses need to be told as well.
Number 1, number 2, number 3.
(Scanning carefully)
Number four. Okay.
Let's go.
(Let's go, Cookie!)
Move out wide and look at number one.
Wider. There you go.
Jump over and turn right.
- That's impressive, Woo Il. - Turn right. Wider.
You don't have to speed up now.
Widen out the line.
There you go. Look at it and turn.
(He looks at obstacle number 2 this time.)
After a year of this,
- you can jump over obstacles. - Gosh!
Wide.
(He also passes obstacle number 2 with ease.)
There you go. Think of the next one.
(Groaning)
- Bring your shoulders back. - These are dangerous moments.
That's intense.
- They had to go over that one. - Gosh, he almost fell off.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
This is what happens.
You fall off if you lose your balance.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
The obstacles are set up like this.
The jump has to be done right in the middle...
for the horse not to get surprised.
- When we're toward the side, - The horse wouldn't jump.
it would see the block...
and make a sudden turn after being surprised.
- That's how people end up falling. - Gosh, that's scary!
(Focusing again)
Do it slowly. It doesn't have to be fast.
(He tries the course he failed once again.)
There you go. Bring your shoulders back.
Think of number three.
Slowly. Move your shoulder back.
- Gosh! - Slowly.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong? - What's wrong?
- The horse moved away. - It went the other way.
Have you ever fallen off a horse?
I have.
Wouldn't that traumatize you from doing it again?
Our rhythms didn't match.
The horse and I had to jump up at the same time,
- my bottom went up first... - Oh, gosh!
- and I was hit in mid-air. - You were hit?
- Gosh! - I fell sideways.
- Did you not get hurt? - I did get hurt.
- Where did you get hurt? - Where did you get hurt?
I hurt my shoulder.
I went to the hospital...
and I was told that my shoulder was fractured.
- Gosh! - Right.
- You're really high up. - I just had an arm splint on.
I was still eager to get jobs in that field.
- You're a total beast. - Because of that thought,
- I endured through the pain... - It was a matter of survival.
- Right. - and kept horseback riding.
He's a true man.
He has beastly charms.
Let's do this. Why did you stop?
Let's do this.
(Let's do this.)
Okay.
(Terrius sets off once again after making a big resolution.)
I started getting competitive.
(We can do this.)
Out wide.
There you go. Shoulders back.
(He moves past the obstacle as if he was one with Cookie.)
Change direction and go toward the next one.
- The next one. - This is the tough one.
This isn't easy to do.
(He almost fell off at this spot.)
Change direction and go toward the next one.
- Slowly. - He did it!
Slowly.
One, two, three. There you go.
(He looks a lot more relaxed now.)
(Terrius is here on his white horse!)
Good. Don't speed up.
(He goes for the next obstacle with a boost of confidence.)
Two, three.
Good. Move out wide and aim for the double.
(He turns naturally.)
Keep your back straight. Aim for the middle.
Change.
Great job.
(The double jump was done nicely as well.)
Gosh!
Look at it.
"Let's be at the top when it comes to horseback riding."
I did it with that sort of mindset.
(To become Korea's number 1)
There you go.
Are you planning to be in competitions as well?
I already competed in one.
- Really? - What happened?
- An amateur competition? - I wasn't a pro equestrian...
and it was for an event match.
I did compete with others just like in an actual competition.
- I see. How did you do? - Right.
Based on my record,
I think I placed around 3rd to 4th.
Slowly.
(He focuses on his training to become number 1.)
Change. Next one.
Change. There you go. Move out wide.
Gosh.
- That's impressive. - That's really impressive.
Don't be too fast.
I rode the horse quite a lot that day.
Usually, I would be on the horse for a quick session.
I was on the horse for a quite a while that day.
(Practicing hard as if it was an actual competition)
(The effort to become Korea's number 1)
Go over number 8 and number 1.
Number two.
The horse has to be complimented right away.
- Compliment within three seconds. - Great job.
Okay. Today's lesson ends here.
- Great work. - Great work.
- Gosh, great work, Cookie. - You did well.
- You did well today. - Gosh, great work.
(Stopping)
My legs are shaking.
(Shaking)
So your legs shake even after a year of this.
- Gosh. - Your legs look very nice.
(Groaning)
Gosh.
(The after-effects make him groan automatically.)
Gosh, look at his legs.
Are his legs okay?
- Does it feel like a leg workout? - I guess so.
Right.
(Swaying)
You're like that even after a year of this.
Goodbye!
You feel proud after a leg workout.
- Just like at the gym. - I see.
Right. That's a great workout.
("Stigma" by Yim Jae Beom)
(As if my heart was burnt)
("For You" by Yim Jae Beom)
(My wild thoughts and anxious eyes)
(Woo Il heads back to Seoul while singing Yim Jae Beom's songs.)
You're back home.
The navigation will now end.
(Humming)
(His hair sways back and forth.)
He has so much hair.
(Has he gone to a restaurant?)
- You went there? - Yes.
What is this place?
- This place is... - I should've gone there too.
really popular.
(Flustered)
- It's closed. - I went there too early.
(Is it not opening time yet?)
(Surprised)
What is it?
It's Yun Hwa.
(Hong Yun Hwa and Kim Min Gi)
What was that? Why did you close the door?
(Min Gi, Yun Hwa)
(The loveable cutie of the comedy world)
She's so cute.
(And a fool for Yun Hwa who only thinks about his wife)
- They dated for ten years, - That's right.
and they still love each other so much.
They're still newlyweds.
They look at each other with so much love.
Why did you close the door?
- Because we're not open yet. - Is that so?
But it's 12pm.
We're getting ready.
- Is that so? - Why are you limping?
- Did you hurt your legs? - No, I went to ride a horse.
- What did you do? - Horseback riding.
- You went horseback riding? - Yes.
I just got back from it.
Oh, you get ready to open at this hour.
We have to get ready to open the bar.
It's really cute and charming.
Comedian Kim Min Gi and Hong Yun Hwa...
are running this bar together.
Yes.
Yun Hwa knows I live alone,
so she always packs side dishes for me.
She packs me side dishes and soup.
- Yun Hwa is a good cook. - She packs them for me.
She always packs the side dishes for me when I go there.
The bar that Yun Hwa...
and Min Gi Run is near my place.
She told me she'd pack me some side dishes,
so I dropped by on my way home.
Generally,
you shouldn't have your hair down at a restaurant.
When you're at a restaurant, you need to keep your hair neat.
That's right.
When the bar opens,
what does Min Gi do, and what do you do?
- What are your roles? - I manage the front-of-house.
- I manage the front-of-house. - I manage the front-of-house.
- Yun Hwa manages the kitchen. - Right. I manage the kitchen.
Min Gi manages the outdoor seats and the dining area.
So your hair can never fall.
I know.
- Were you there to help? - That's right.
I felt bad to get her side dishes for free,
so I went to help them get ready to open the bar...
and earn her side dishes.
I should've worn a hat.
Even with a hat, people with long hair must tie it tight.
- I know. - Look at their teamwork.
- Let me see. How neat. - Is it okay?
So then my hair won't fall?
- We're sorry, Jung. - How cute.
Okay.
What am I doing today?
I need to get groceries now.
- Where do you get your groceries? - Mangwon Market.
- Oh, Mangwon Market? - It's right there.
You get your groceries there?
I see. All right.
Didn't you bring your jacket?
It's not cold now.
We'll have to ride a motorcycle.
- You'll be cold on it. - Not at all.
You ride a motorcycle?
Yes, Yun Hwa rides one.
How am I supposed to go?
You can get on the back.
- At the back of you? - Yes.
- Wouldn't it be unstable? Really? - Come on, Woo Il.
- I've ridden it for seven years. - Really?
- Seven years? Really? - Yes.
I ride that motorcycle when I go grocery shopping.
- I feel like she's a good driver. - She is.
Let's go now. For the opening...
There are many dishes we need to make in advance.
- It'll be really cold. - I'll be fine. The wind is...
It's not cold.
What? Where is the motorcycle?
Can both of us ride it?
(Are you sure the two of us can ride this?)
- It doesn't... - It doesn't fit?
All right.
It's okay. It's right in front.
Goodness. Wait a minute.
Min Gi will be unhappy about it.
- Woo Il! - Woo Il.
- Grab the back, not Yun Hwa. - I mean...
- Don't grab her! - He's mad for real.
- He really is. - He is.
- I'm a bit anxious. - Come on.
- I took Gi Ru home on this too. - Really? Okay.
Drive slowly.
Check the left side.
You should check the left side!
I did!
- Where are you going? - Look at how he's adoring her.
That fool for Yun Hwa.
- See you later. - See you. We'll be right back.
- I drive a motorcycle really well. - That's good.
(Exclaiming)
Go slowly.
- Come on, Woo Il. - Yes?
Trust me.
I've rarely ridden on the back of someone's motorcycle.
Motorcycle riders don't get on the back, do they?
No.
All right. That's great. There you go.
It's red light.
Yun Hwa is good.
That's cute.
Gosh, don't get too close.
Gosh, the car is coming.
- Woo Il, trust me! - Okay.
You're making me more anxious!
If you don't drive it, you get nervous.
If the driver hears that, they become more anxious.
You have to trust them since you're on it.
You should check the surroundings for unprotected left turns.
I did!
- That means you're not protected. - He sounds just like my mom!
(A man who knows how to ride a motorcycle)
- Are you a king of nagging? - You don't know...
when you might get into an accident.
You need to make a quick decision.
- But... - You shouldn't delay at all.
This is really good. Keeping a distance.
It's because cars... Yes, you should be careful with these.
- Be careful. - I'm going at 20km per hour.
That's it.
You nag too much.
I feel like you will make me sick.
I think I'll get sick.
Drivers usually don't get carsick.
- But I feel like I will. - They don't get sick.
Gosh, look at the fall leaves. My goodness.
(Blocking his nagging)
(The leaves turned yellow)
We're here.
- It's here. - All right.
- Mangwon Market. Goodness. - This market is really nice.
The chili fritter from there is really good.
Yes, it is. The croquettes are good too.
What should we buy?
Onions and fruits.
(Amazed)
(Mangwon Market)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- You can't walk past that smell. - I love it.
(Filled with food that make you salivate)
Goodness.
- That's really good. - This is really delicious.
- My gosh. - I know.
(Mangwon Market with 40 years of history has everything.)
- This is amazing. - Woo Il.
Seven abalones are ten dollars.
Our bar used to sell abalones,
and we got them from here.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
- Hello. - Oh, hello.
Oh, hello.
(Saying hello cheerfully)
She's close with everyone there because she always shops there.
What do they sell there?
That side...
There are shops I go often.
- Over that side? - Yes.
- Of course there are. - She knows all the shops there.
(Thinking)
Wait. Tteokbokki...
Should we have some tteokbokki?
- They have mini gimbap too. - And mini gimbap?
I didn't get to eat anything after horseback riding.
I was hungry then.
- Gosh, it looks good. - You came here last time too.
- That's right. - You came here before?
I did.
- You're a regular here. - I came here.
- Goodness. - Gosh, it's good.
- Goodness. What do I do? - It's really good.
(The perfect sides that are light and savory)
Mini gimbap.
- This one. - Is this gimmari, ma'am?
- Yes. - You must make them yourself.
- It's huge. - Shall we have one gimmari...
- with tteokbokki? - That sounds good.
Which gimbap are you going to have?
I like spicy fishcake gimbap.
- Spam. - Spam. What else?
- Tteokgalbi. - Tteokgalbi?
That? Okay.
- What else? - Are you treating me?
Yes, it's on me.
- Are you treating me? - Yes, it's on me.
I can't believe it.
- Are you really treating me? - I will.
- She's really surprised. - For real?
Go ahead and eat.
It must be a first for Yun Hwa.
- I know. It's really strange. - I know.
I can't believe it.
- I'm going to eat it now. - Go ahead.
She must find it hard to believe.
That must be so good, Yun Hwa!
- Gosh, look. That's so much. - Thank you.
She gave us this and fishcake too.
- Goodness. - She put it in tteokbokki.
- Goodness. - That looks good.
Gosh, the gimmari is filled.
Gosh, the gimmari looks good.
(Dipping mini gimbap deep in the tteokbokki soup)
I should be careful.
(It's even more delicious because Woo Il bought it for me.)
It's so good.
- It's really good. - Thank you.
(She can't help but give a thumbs-up.)
I hope Woo Il will become richer.
(So I can eat more.)
(Taking a bite)
Gosh, it's so good. The fritter is really good too.
(Amazed)
- Which one does he like? - Min Gi?
- Min Gi likes spicy fishcake. - Packing some for Min Gi too?
- Okay. Pick one more. - Burdock gimbap.
- That's really nice. - Let's pack this for Min Gi.
- What about fritters? - Can I get them too?
Yes, get some fritters.
Would you like fritters too?
We'll take one gimmari.
(Packing gimmari as well)
It's all set.
(Slurping in one last time)
Gosh, the soup is so good.
Is it packed already?
Gosh, no way. Woo Il is paying. I need to take a video of this.
- Gosh, he must've never paid. - Gosh.
- This way, you will... - You need to leave proof.
(Turning on the camera right away)
(He's so thrifty that he has coffee from the day before.)
(He helps organize other people's fridges.)
(A thrifty spender famous among comedians)
Yun Hwa helped me a lot before,
and now, I can...
spend that much for her.
That gives me happiness.
(He happily treated her to a meal.)
- How much is it, ma'am? - It's 12 dollars.
It's 12 dollars, Woo Il!
He spent a lot.
(Proving the class of Terrius by spending 12 dollars)
Thank you. Could you throw the receipt?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It was delicious.
- Have a good one. - I enjoyed it, Woo Il.
All right.
My good deeds continue.
You call that a good deed?
Then Hyun Moo must be a fairy.
(Splurging on good deeds)
- I'm a fairy, then. - He's the Jade Emperor.
(Jade Emperor Moomoo)
Gosh, it'll be really good if you grill that fish.
It's amazing. Gosh, sushi!
Gosh, that's seven dollars?
- Really? - It's so cheap.
We'll take one salmon sushi.
What's going on?
That means you spent 19 dollars today.
(After he's let loose by spending 12 dollars...)
Please ring me up.
Sir, we'll take three bags of rice puffs.
- Three? - Yes.
Hold on. This...
(Let me get my wallet.)
- I'll get it for you. - Goodness.
No, Woo Il. You spent 19 dollars today.
Look at her face. She's serious.
- Yes, she's not trying to be funny. - She's not.
No, Woo Il. You spent 19 dollars today.
(12 dollars, 7 dollars, and rice puffs too?)
When something like that happens,
we take a video and share it...
- in the comedian group chat. - You share it?
- So... - "Woo Il finally treated me."
- Like this? - "Woo Il treated me to a meal."
And people will go, "Oh, my. Really? He must be crazy."
"My goodness. I can't believe it."
I think there will be a notice about it in the comedian group chat.
- You spent a lot. - Gosh, Woo Il, what's wrong?
I'll pay for it.
- Woo Il. - You can pay for the groceries.
Aren't you spending too much?
I can spend that much because Yun Hwa helped me a lot.
Why does it taste different?
This place is really good.
I'll get going, sir!
Bye.
(Look! It's Terrius!)
Word will get around.
- He's popular. - Thank you.
(Getting all the attention from the people at the market)
I've been negligent of market popularity lately.
(I should work harder.)
(They begin getting groceries in earnest.)
Sir, for Shine Muscat...
This looks good. We'll take this.
They're huge.
Here you go.
Yun Hwa is getting the expensive ones.
- Have a good day. - You too.
- Hope you make lots of sales. - Bye.
- Oh, meat? - Yes.
I need to get dried lavers too.
- Dried lavers? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hi.
Sir, I'll get some dried lavers.
Their dried lavers are really good.
(Dried lavers grilled on spot)
Grilled dried lavers from a market.
I'll take five packs of dried lavers.
- Five? I'll get them for you. - Oh, my.
(Hold on.)
Hold on.
I transferred it.
Woo Il.
You have more than 1,000 dollars.
(Woo Il is rich!)
- Have a good day. - My good deeds continue.
(Feeling proud)
On the field day,
I enjoyed the meal so much.
So I prepared something for you.
- What's gotten into you? - Is it rice puffs?
- What is it? - My good deeds will continue.
- What is it? - You brought it?
(What? What is it?)
It's dried lavers.
- Is it really dried lavers? - Is it really dried lavers?
It's that dried lavers.
I got you the dried lavers.
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
They're all cut,
- so just have it as is. - Goodness.
Is it a piece per person?
- No, I got ten of these. - Oh, you got more?
- Ten packs. - Why did you get so many?
I got ten packs,
but I ate one for myself.
So I brought nine.
(I brought nine.)
(There are five people, and you brought nine packs?)
Why did you have to make it iffy?
It's not iffy.
I got nine, so that's more than enough, isn't it?
- It's iffy. - It is.
One of us will take just one.
Someone has to take one pack.
I'll just take one.
- No, I'll take one. - No, let me.
- I... - I'm serious.
- I won't take it. - I'll take just one.
- Forget it. - What will that make Hyun Moo?
- It's really fine. - You take it.
- It's okay. - You guys can take it.
Don't get me wrong. I don't really like dried lavers.
(Yum)
There's a Korean...
- who doesn't like dried lavers? - Yes, me.
- I don't like dried lavers. - It gets awkward.
I know. Who's going to take two?
- And who will take one? - I'll take one.
It's really iffy.
- What do we do? - Let's just take them.
- Can we? Can we take them? - Yes, let's take one each.
It's the thought that counts.
Goodness. Thank you, Woo Il.
- And it's vacuum-sealed. - Grilled lavers from a market.
- Thank you. - Goodness.
Thank you for this, Woo Il.
Thank you so much, Woo Il.
Thank you.
This is too good to eat.
I should take a photo of this as proof.
Yes, I'm going to frame it.
I think we can do that.
- This is... - Yes.
more precious than Lingard's uniform.
- Gosh, of course it is. - Of course.
Let's all take a photo while holding it.
- Woo Il... - Hold on.
- Sign your autograph here. - Please sign here.
(Sign your autograph here liker Lingard did.)
- That's right. - Sign one for me too!
- Sign your autograph here. - Here.
How can we eat it?
- I can't eat it. - How can we eat it?
Laminate it.
(Their hands are full in no time.)
- Let's go now, Woo Il. - All right.
Gosh, that was great.
(After riding the bike for a while,)
(they return to the bar.)
- Goodness. - Hey.
We got you something to eat so you could eat right away.
- Goodness. - We got you something.
- Do you know how much he spent? - How much?
He spent more than 50 dollars.
Goodness.
- He's become a different man. - He spent more than 50 dollars.
- He got these? - Yes.
He spent more than 50 dollars for us.
No, I didn't pay for everything.
Hey, I got you this so you could eat it right away.
This and gimmari. It's really good.
- Yes. - You like gimmari.
This gimmari is really good.
Hey, this sushi. You should have this sushi.
This couple helped me a lot,
so I had to pay back.
- Gosh, it looks good. - Take that out.
I'll put this in the fridge first.
It looks good.
- Gosh, that looks good. - It looks solid.
(Taking a bite of the sushi Woo Il got for him)
Woo Il.
- This... - The radish is delicious.
Woo Il, did you finish the one I gave you last time?
- I did. - You did already?
It's because...
it's good as a side dish.
But it goes well with ramyeon too.
- Right. It's delicious, right? - Yes.
Then you should take this too.
What is it? What's that?
(Bringing a mysterious bag)
- She's giving so much. - This is...
- What's this? - Take one each.
Since you'll be having it by yourself,
have a fruit each.
This is fresh kimchi.
Fresh kimchi? Nice.
- You must have it today. - Okay.
This is salted seafood.
- Salted seafood? What kind? - I packed a bit of everything.
- This is salted octopus. - Oh, there are different kinds.
This is salted pollack roe, and this is salted pollack intestine.
This is seasoned raw pollack.
How generous of her.
She packed it appropriately for people who live alone.
This is from Jeju.
You know the thing that was modified with hwanggeumhyang.
Goodness, that's precious.
You should have one per day only.
You have high blood sugar.
She's worried about his high blood sugar too.
All right, thank you.
Take this too.
- A foam roller? - Yes, that.
- Take this too. - She's giving everything.
That must cost more than 50 dollars.
Yun Hwa is really generous.
He's taking twice as much.
Hey, this is too much. It's really fine.
Gosh, lucky I got paper towels.
(The bag is already full.)
We should hold a flea market someday.
For real. Don't just talk.
I'm serious.
Really? Then are you willing to take some?
Of course. For sure.
Don't we have a lot of stuff that he must want?
- All of us have a lot. - We...
have so much stuff.
- We must share them. - We really should.
- Take this bag like this, okay? - Okay.
I'll get going.
Woo Il, please help him clean.
- Me? - Okay.
- I'll get going. - Where is she going?
Yun Hwa had some work.
There are spiderwebs between the gaps.
Oh, here? Like this?
Roll the spiderwebs with this to remove them.
I was trying to help.
- You should earn your keep. - Oh, like these?
You need a health certificate to work at a restaurant.
I got one, actually.
I have to insert a cotton swab...
into your anus 3cm deep and remove it.
That must hurt a lot.
It's also my wonder...
why that is the only way to check for typhoid.
Thanks to them, you checked to see if you had typhoid.
You passed.
(Thanks to them, he got to check that he's healthy.)
It's nice that you're helping.
- Right. - We get to prepare for winter.
This is quite pleasing.
That's right.
He said they got spiderwebs quicker than they thought.
- I can see. - They get it in a day?
They keep getting them after a day.
- Gosh. For real. - It's all good.
(Thanks to Woo Il, it's become clean.)
- It's clean. Oh, my. - There are many gaps.
(Brushing)
(He cleans the street in front of the bar as well.)
(Thanks to him, it becomes clean.)
He's diligent and good.
There you go.
(Brushing the sidewalk blocks with a brush as well)
There were a lot of bird droppings as there was a tree.
It's a sidewalk in front of the bar,
so some people wait in line on that sidewalk.
- If they see bird droppings, - Right.
- it might not look hygienic. - Right.
Woo Il is good.
(Brushing harder than anyone)
Shouldn't I be rewarded by the district office at this rate?
I got more eager to clean as it got cleaner.
Woo Il did most of the work on the field day too.
There are so many bird droppings.
(Working hard)
(Surprised)
- It's good, right? Okay. - Yes.
- It's clean. - It's neat.
- Yes. - For real.
It's clean.
(He continues to clean the inside as well.)
He helped a lot.
(Cleaning every table without missing one)
(Cleaning the sides thoroughly as well)
(A part-timer who takes care of things on his own)
Normally, people sit on the inside first.
I'm really happy these days.
It was tiring to go horseback riding...
and help Yun Hwa and Min Gi,
But this is also proof that I've changed.
I can be that generous, at least.
Today was tiring, but it was filling.
That's what I thought.
I'll get going. Thanks for this!
- Bye, Woo Il. - Bye. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- I'll text Yun Hwa. Thank you. - Okay.
Bye.
You're taking so much stuff.
- He helped a lot, though. - Bye!
He cleaned outside and inside as well.
(This is the Class of Terrius)
(Next story)
(The day she went to clean her grandparents' place)
(She shared her worry with Hyun Moo and Kian84.)
(You should keep him.)
(I'll help you.)
(With their sincere support,)
(Na Rae plucked up her courage.)
(Introducing Na Rae's new family)
(It's been two months and a half since they started living together.)
(The house is already filled with Bok Dol's stuff.)
(I think my dog...)
(is a genius.)
(He's really smart.)
Wait.
(Focused)
(Good job!)
(You smart dog!)
(Let's get you dressed, my genius dog.)
(I can't miss out on styling my dog.)
(It's really cute.)
(Shall we try it on?)
(You'll become the best dog.)
(Your food will have to be special too.)
(I'll give you the best of the best things.)
(It's time for tutoring.)
(Just fully trust me.)
(For my dog,)
(I can do this much.)
(I'm dog tired.)
It's a mess.
(Sky Castle for Dogs)
(Ji Hyeon is opening a box?)
(He took out a skate from it?)
(Today, he's hosting an important guest.)
(Hitting)
(Skillful)
(Skillfully showing off how to prepare a skate)
(Here comes Park Skate.)
(Gosh, it's so nice.)
(All kinds of delicacies from Mokpo are here.)
(Filling the container with love for the important guest)
(Packing a bundle is no problem.)
(Taking care of his looks is also no problem.)
(The place he reached after packing so much stuff)
(The important guest can be seen from afar.)
(Bowing)
How have you been?
(It's Ji Hyun's idol, Singer Nam Jin.)
(It's the 60th year since his debut.)
The living legend.
(The first dance singer of Korea)
(You'd be a spy if you don't know him.)
(The representative singer from Mokpo, Ji Hyeon's hometown,)
(Nam Jin)
(You're quite tall.)
(Awkward)
(You have the right attitude.)
(Becoming naturally polite at the godfather's charisma)
(You haven't eaten yet?)
(I didn't, so I can eat this a lot.)
(It's long-arm octopus.)
(Or three-legged octopus.)
(Pardon?)
(The senior's dazzling wit...)
(keeps coming without pause.)
(Polite)
(And...)
(Glaring)
(He ended up making a mistake?)
(With My Dear)
(With My Charismatic Senior)